axleration.com 2013-08-24

# Privacy Policy | Axleration

We respect your privacy and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy while online at our site [www.axleration.com](http://www.axleration.com/) . The following discloses theinformation gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

**Log Files**  
Like most standard Website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Newsletter**  
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter (powered by Feedburner), we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user computer tied to informationabout the user. Our site don’t use cookies. However, Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Links**  
This Website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Advertisers**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the following ad companies: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies.

**Analytics**

We use Google Analytics to track the visitor data. Google Analytics uses cookies to track visitor information, but no personally identifiable information such as your IP address is not stored.

**Contact  Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions **regarding our privacy policy** , please contact us through the Privacy Issues form below for other purposes, contact us [here](http://www.axleration.com/contact-us/).

[contact-form-7 id="10114" title="Privacy Issues"]

[  
  
](http://twitter.com/share?url=http://axleration.com/privacy-policy/&text=Privacy%20Policy "Click here if you like this article.")
